Shouldn't there be more fabric?
Nah, that's pretty standard.
I wonder if Hinata will like this one...
Don't worry, Bell. Be confident!
Up we go.
Hinata!
Sorry for the wait.
It's hot!
The summers in this world are brutal.
It's even worse than usual this year.
Hinata...
It's too hot to walk!
W-We're almost home, so hang in there!
Hinata! Why are you
avoiding me all of a sudden?!
I-I'm not...
I can't tell her that I'm
hyperaware of her now!
What's the matter?
Hi-na-ta!
I knew it... You are avoiding me!
Y-You surprised me just now, is all!
Then give me a big hug!
Make it even hotter than
this stupid weather!
U-Um... Maybe we shouldn't in public...
Oh, come on! Why not?!
Hey, you guys!
Let's go to the beach on our next day off!
The beach?
Yeah!
It's the perfect weather for it,
and I think it'd be a nice change of pace.
Plus, I'm sure Sunohara would be thrilled
to see you wearing a cute swimsuit, Bell.
A cute swimsuit...?
Hi-na-ta!
B-Bell...
You look so sexy like that...
I can't... hold back any longer!
Oh, Hinata!
You've finally decided to be
honest with yourself!
Let's go, Hinata! Right now!
Now?!
If we go now, it'd be getting dark out
by the time we arrive.
Then when can we go?!
Next Sunday, maybe?
We'll have to go swimsuit shopping, too.
Make sure to get my good side!
W-Wait, slow down!
We ended up here after all...
What do you think?
Mhm, it's tasty.
Not the shaved ice.
I was talking about my swimsuit.
Have you seen it?
Take a good... long... hard look.
Bell... Stop, a lot of people
are watching us...
That doesn't matter to me.
I chose this swimsuit
especially for you, Hinata.
I look much tastier than shaved ice, don't I?
Uh... W-Well, you aren't food,
so I don't know about "tasty"...
Okay, fine!
It's strawberry-flavored.
Want a taste?
Go right ahead.
No, don't be swayed!
You swore you were going to do this right!
Do you not like my swimsuit...?
N-No, that's not it!
Then how about this?
Huh?!
Not your cup of tea?
Then what about this one?
Bell!
Tell me which style you prefer.
I'll wear anything you
want me to wear, Hinata.
Even something like this.
So, which one's your favorite?
What are you doing?!
Using magic on a crowded beach?
Are you trying to annoy Lord Hinata again?
You just had to tag along...
Who are you to decide how he feels?!
Cecil!
Bell!
Wanna play beach volleyball with us?
Volleyball?
I'll pass. I might get a sunburn.
Aw...
Then let me put some sunscreen on you!
Good idea! Nobody likes
a sunburn, am I right?
Hinata! Will you put sunscreen on—
I-I gotta go to the bathroom!
Seriously?!
Let's slather it on there!
Oof, you're tense, Cecil.
Working in an office is tough.
You have just the prettiest skin, Bell.
It's as radiant as a gem!
Yeah, Hinata said the same thing...
He's avoiding me, isn't he?
Am I annoying him...?
Does he need space...?
Bell...
Sakura! What was that for?!
You're going soft on me, Bell!
I mean...
You and Sunohara are
destined for each other, right?
Remember what you told me before?
"I'll never leave Hinata's side ever again."
Hearing you say that really inspired me!
Don't worry.
Knowing Sunohara, it'll all work out.
Sakura...
Sorry, my hand slipped...
It's dripping everywhere...
Can you wipe it off?
Are you okay? I'll grab a towel!
Sakura!
I-I'm sorry...
Mariabell!
Quit laughing and help us!
My bad!
Cheers!
Mm, smells good!
It looks yummy!
Just a little longer and they'll be done.
A barbeque at the beach...
This is pretty nice.
Okay, let's dig in!
Tasty!
We've got grilled shrimp, too!
Do you want some, Lord Hinata?
Lord Hinata?
Huh? Oh, uh, sure!
I'll have some, thanks!
Stay calm. I'll get it for you.
D-Don't pull too hard!
This should take care of it.
Who'da thunk that thing was alive?
Where are Mariabell and Lord Hinata?
Showers
Whoa, Bell. What's going on with you?
You're the one who's acting weird, Hinata.
It's like you've been avoiding
being alone with me.
That's not true—
Yes, it is!
Hinata...
You didn't actually want to
come to the beach, did you?
It's either that, or...
do you really not like me anymore?
No, that isn't—
Yeah, I know.
Huh?
I know you could never hate me, Hinata.
And even if you somehow did hate me,
I know you would never, ever
avoid me like this.
Bell...
I can tell that something's been
bothering you lately.
And I can tell that it has
something to do with me.
But listen, Hinata...
I can't stand to see you suffer
because of me.
You're my whole world.
No... I care more about you
than I do myself.
A little intense like always,
but also... kind.
I'm sorry, Bell.
I feel better now.
Really?
Yeah.
Good. I'm glad.
W-Well, we should probably head back.
How about we... make up first?
M-Make up, as in...?
You had me worried, so...
I could use some reassurance.
W-We can't, Bell!
But you don't hate me, do you?
Of course I don't!
But I... have to do things right!
Okay, we'll do it right.
Alright, let's wrap it up!
Should we try swimming
further out together?
Absolutely!
Race you guys to that rock over there!
Ready... go!
Wait up!
Not surprising for an adventurer
who defeated the Demon Lord...
We should go, too!
Sounds good.
What's the matter, Bell?
The truth is...
I have a confession to make.
Wh-What is it?
I... can't swim.
Huh?
Whaaaaat?!